<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Mom of Wild Gals</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 23:51:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Long-MOWG-logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Mom of Wild Gals</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Hello world!</title>
		<link>/2023/01/07/hello-world/</link>
					<comments>/2023/01/07/hello-world/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[alyssa]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 23:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2023/01/07/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title></title>
		<link>/2023/01/01/stress-free-2023/</link>
					<comments>/2023/01/01/stress-free-2023/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[alyssa]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 06:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Life]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://momofwildgals.com/?p=111</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[What a fun mantra and resolution that would be but oh my, how unrealistic. I don’t necessarily do resolutions but I am going to give myself a word for this year. I find that resolutions, for me, can often be tasks I get excited about, and then I have one or two bad days and [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>What a fun mantra and resolution that would be but oh my, how unrealistic. I don’t necessarily do resolutions but I am going to give myself a word for this year. I find that resolutions, for me, can often be tasks I get excited about, and then I have one or two bad days and feel like I’ve failed. I just don’t have the capacity for that added pressure.&nbsp;</p>



<p>A word is something I can focus on, and pray about, and that can cover many aspects of my life.&nbsp;</p>



<p>My word for 2023 is&nbsp;<strong>mindful</strong>.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Mindful by definition means conscious or aware of something.&nbsp;</p>



<p>This past year was truly a year of learning and growth for me. I was pregnant and birthed our third daughter (after infertility, loss, and being told I couldn’t carry another baby I ended up carrying two more- that’s a story for another time), traveled, learned a lot, and decided to make changes to the life we are creating in our home.&nbsp;</p>



<p>After having our baby in October, I began a journey of making our home have less clutter, I started to learn about ways to put systems in so all of us can contribute to our home in a less stressful way, and I began reading about how we would like to raise our children.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Mindful seems appropriate for the season I am in. I plan to be mindful to carve out time for things that are important to me like reading my Bible, reading a book, and writing for this blog. I plan to be mindful of the ingredients in our food, the shows we allow our children to watch, the items we keep and bring into our home, and the people we spend time with.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Hopefully, I can look back at the end of 2023 and think “wow, I mindfully worked on creating the life I want”.&nbsp;</p>



<p>So here is to more mindful moments. Happy New Year.&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2023/01/01/stress-free-2023/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title></title>
		<link>/2022/12/31/106/</link>
					<comments>/2022/12/31/106/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[alyssa]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 18:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Parenting]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://momofwildgals.com/?p=106</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I see so many toxic infant feeding posts every day, it makes me nauseous. Posts saying “I only breastfed for two weeks”, “I hate pumping”, “I only get one ounce”, etc.&#160; Your worth is not defined by how many ounces of breastmilk you produce and it is not defined by whether you breastfeed or formula-feed [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h1 class="wp-block-heading"></h1>



<p>I see so many toxic infant feeding posts every day, it makes me nauseous. Posts saying “I only breastfed for two weeks”, “I hate pumping”, “I only get one ounce”, etc.&nbsp;</p>



<p id="worth">Your worth is not defined by how many ounces of breastmilk you produce and it is not defined by whether you breastfeed or formula-feed your child. We have to be so intentional with our words as mamas and need to remind ourselves that what works for us or our baby, doesn’t always work for another mama and baby.&nbsp;</p>



<p>We have to start recognizing when advice can become toxic and not helpful because motherhood is so fragile. When you seek support and advice from others remember:&nbsp;</p>



<ol>
<li>This is advice, not a directive. I can choose to read this and not do anything with this information</li>



<li>I asked for support, this may not be the support I thought I was going to get but this is how this person is showing up today, they’re doing their best.&nbsp;</li>



<li>This person may have said something hurtful but I’m going to choose to either not respond or to respond with kindness.&nbsp;</li>



<li>What works for one person, may not work for me (or my body, or my baby, or my mental health).&nbsp;</li>
</ol>



<p>When you see things on social media or hear things from other parents- take the little nuggets of support and help you need and leave the rest.&nbsp;</p>



<p>What you’re doing for your baby is enough. Your worth is not defined by how you feed your baby.</p>



<p>Hang in there mamas, we’ve got this.</p>



<p></p>



<p></p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2022/12/31/106/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You don’t have to practice your traditions.</title>
		<link>/2022/12/25/95/</link>
					<comments>/2022/12/25/95/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[alyssa]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 04:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Parenting]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://momofwildgals.com/?p=95</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There I said it. Life is always changing. You have a baby, someone dies, you lost a job, you started a new job, you end up sick through the holidays, or whatever it may be, life isn’t always the same. Last year you may have had the capacity to bake the cookies and watch all [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p></p>



<p>There I said it. Life is always changing. You have a baby, someone dies, you lost a job, you started a new job, you end up sick through the holidays, or whatever it may be, life isn’t always the same. Last year you may have had the capacity to bake the cookies and watch all the Christmas movies, whereas this year you may have no time to do anything but survive and that is OK. </p>



<p>Let me say that again, it is OK to do what you have the capacity to do in the current season of your life. </p>



<p>The holiday season always brings a lot of anxiety. The responsibility we have as parents to obtain perfection for our children often feels heavy and unattainable because it is. Perfection is relative. What I find to be perfect, my husband may find to be annoying and stressful. </p>



<p>This Christmas I am being intentional and choosing to slow down. I didn’t write the family year recap to include in my holiday cards, I didn’t buy all the teachers gifts, and we made a plan as a family about what cookies we wanted to bake instead of making all of them. </p>



<p>So remember, You can do whatever you want to do for the holidays. You can stick with whatever traditions you have, you can create new traditions, or you can do different traditions every year. </p>



<p>Don’t allow things on your to-do list to become tasks you feel obligated to do. Let’s bring joy back to our hearts and only do things that are intentional to maintain that joy. </p>



<p>Merry Christmas, everyone.</p>



<p></p>



<p>PS. Check out our favorite holiday treat <a href="https://momofwildgals.com/recipes/oreo-truffles/">here</a>. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2022/12/25/95/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dear Military Spouse</title>
		<link>/2022/12/25/dear-military-spouse/</link>
					<comments>/2022/12/25/dear-military-spouse/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[alyssa]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 03:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Military Life]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://momofwildgals.com/?p=84</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[You often go without recognition. You take bullets in the form of words- being called “dependa” and your children get called “brats”. Your integrity and reasoning for marrying your service member is often questioned and said “it’s just for the BAH, for the discounts, for Tricare”. Then on top of all of this you get [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>You often go without recognition. You take bullets in the form of words- being called “dependa” and your children get called “brats”. Your integrity and reasoning for marrying your service member is often questioned and said “it’s just for the BAH, for the discounts, for Tricare”. </p>



<p>Then on top of all of this you get told “you knew what you were getting into” or my absolute favorite “<strong>you chose this life</strong>” when you have any sort of human moment that shows weakness because this life isn’t easy. </p>



<p>I want you to know, <strong>I see you</strong>. I see you juggling your schedule, your kids schedules, the FRG, play dates, work, cleaning, cooking, appointments, and good friendships that are few and far between. I see you doing all of this all by yourself, without ONE single person to rely on to help you. I see you working retail jobs and putting your career on hold so he can have his while you care for the family. I see you writing someone you don’t even know down as an emergency contact and I see the worry on your face as you think to yourself that you hope an emergency truly doesn’t happen. I see you as you deal with emergency situations without your spouse or family by your side. I see you turn down calling the red cross because you can handle broken bones or surgery without interfering the mission. I see the bags under your eyes because you were up late waiting for a phone call, an email, or some sort of sign that your service member is OK and thinking of you. I see your compassion and your love for your spouse as you patiently wait for them to come home. I see your tired, overwhelmed, tear filled face when they come home. I see you let your children hug your service member first despite you wanting to jump into their arms. </p>



<p>And most importantly, <strong>I see how you don’t choose this life</strong>. You choose your spouse, no matter what job they have, no matter what obstacles come with it- you choose your spouse- every single day.</p>



<p>Don’t let anyone discredit you. You didn’t know this life you were getting into and the only benefit you’re in for is the love you have with your spouse. </p>



<p>I’m so proud of you for all you do- for being a solid foundation for your family through your service members time of service and for always choosing your spouse despite what the job description is. </p>



<p>Keep on hanging on. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2022/12/25/dear-military-spouse/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Our Favorite Treat</title>
		<link>/2022/12/24/oreo-truffles/</link>
					<comments>/2022/12/24/oreo-truffles/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[alyssa]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:22:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Recipes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://momofwildgals.com/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Oreo truffles are a favorite in our house. Although they may not be a family heirloom recipe, it is one that has been around in our family for some time. Oreo truffles are a delicious and easy-to-make treat that combines crumbled Oreo cookies with cream cheese to form a rich and creamy center. They are [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Oreo truffles are a favorite in our house. Although they may not be a family heirloom recipe, it is one that has been around in our family for some time.</p>



<p>Oreo truffles are a delicious and easy-to-make treat that combines crumbled Oreo cookies with cream cheese to form a rich and creamy center. They are then coated in chocolate, creating a decadent and indulgent dessert that is perfect for any occasion. They are often served at parties or as a sweet snack, and are a hit with both kids and adults alike. Whether you prefer them plain or dressed up with toppings like sprinkles or nuts, Oreo truffles are sure to satisfy your sweet tooth.</p>



<p>Find the recipe <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Oreo-Truffles-MOWG.pdf" data-type="URL" data-id="/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/Oreo-Truffles-MOWG.pdf" target="_blank">here</a>. Enjoy! </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2022/12/24/oreo-truffles/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
